{	"div":
	[	
		{
			"Problem":"3828/78",
			"answer":"3828/78",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"1559/10",
			"answer":"1559/10",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"7073/25",
			"answer":"7073/25",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"4042/59",
			"answer":"4042/59",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"4362/58",
			"answer":"4362/58",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"1260/1.5",
			"answer":"1260/1.5",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"261.3/39",
			"answer":"261.3/39",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"7.392/77",
			"answer":"7.392/77",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"0.594/66",
			"answer":"0.594/66",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"17.63/4.3",
			"answer":"17.63/4.3",
			"status":"unsolved"
		}
	]
}